{"qid":"hard-dblp-0000","question":"How many common collaborators does Jonathan A. Noel have with Zdenek Dvorak?","answer":3}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0001","question":"How many common collaborators does CR Chowdhury have with Jhareswar Maiti?","answer":2}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0002","question":"How many common collaborators does Florian Quinkert have with Thorsten Holz?","answer":2}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0003","question":"How many common collaborators does Gennaro Cordasco have with Carmine Spagnuolo?","answer":5}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0004","question":"How many common collaborators does Enrique Corona have with Armin Parchami?","answer":5}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0005","question":"How many common collaborators does Ehsan Rahiminejad have with Mahmood Amiri?","answer":2}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0006","question":"How many common collaborators does Todd J. Green have with Doug Terry?","answer":22}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0007","question":"How many common collaborators does Fatemeh Homayounieh have with Mannudeep Kalra?","answer":7}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0008","question":"How many common collaborators does Chunqiu Xia have with Sai Teja Peddinti?","answer":3}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0009","question":"How many common collaborators does David E Gloriam have with Stefan Mordalski?","answer":3}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0010","question":"How many common collaborators does Baokai Cheng have with Hai Xiao?","answer":1}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0011","question":"How many common collaborators does Haiying Xia have with Shuxiang Song?","answer":1}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0012","question":"How many common collaborators does Tianbiao Yang have with Jihui Zhao?","answer":8}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0013","question":"How many common collaborators does Jay Mundra have with Raj Snehal?","answer":1}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0014","question":"Which is/are the most cited paper(s) written by Katrina Falkner in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same. If there are multiple papers with the same citations, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"EmoMent: An Emotion Annotated Mental Health Corpus from Two South Asian Countries."}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0015","question":"Which is/are the most cited paper(s) written by Thyne Boonmark in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same. If there are multiple papers with the same citations, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Lux: Always-on Visualization Recommendations for Exploratory Dataframe Workflows."}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0016","question":"Which is/are the most cited paper(s) written by Miroslava Slavcheva in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same. If there are multiple papers with the same citations, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Variational Level Set Evolution for Non-rigid 3D Reconstruction from a Single Depth Camera."}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0017","question":"Which is/are the most cited paper(s) written by C.S. Ramalingam in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same. If there are multiple papers with the same citations, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"A Method With Lower-Than-Mle Threshold Snr For Frequency Estimation Of Multiple Sinusoids"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0018","question":"Which is/are the most cited paper(s) written by Seo Young Oh in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same. If there are multiple papers with the same citations, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Multi-scale Mixed Reality Collaboration for Digital Twin"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0019","question":"Which is/are the most cited paper(s) written by Jiecai Zheng in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same. If there are multiple papers with the same citations, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"UGRec: Modeling Directed and Undirected Relations for Recommendation"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0020","question":"Which is/are the most cited paper(s) written by Enrico Russo in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same. If there are multiple papers with the same citations, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"DNN Model Compression for IoT Domain-Specific Hardware Accelerators"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0021","question":"Which is/are the most cited paper(s) written by Henning Stichtenoth in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same. If there are multiple papers with the same citations, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Asymptotically good towers of function fields with small p-rank"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0022","question":"Which is/are the most cited paper(s) written by Konrad Burnik in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same. If there are multiple papers with the same citations, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Dense computability structures"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0023","question":"Which is/are the most cited paper(s) written by RM Kaplan in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same. If there are multiple papers with the same citations, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"LFG Generation from Acyclic F-Structures is NP-Hard"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0024","question":"Which is/are the most cited paper(s) written by Libor Polčák in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same. If there are multiple papers with the same citations, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Unified SNMP Interface for IoT Monitoring"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0025","question":"Which is/are the most cited paper(s) written by Hoang Thi Huong Giang in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same. If there are multiple papers with the same citations, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Uplink Noma-Based Long-Term Throughput Maximization Scheme For Cognitive Radio Networks: An Actor-Critic Reinforcement Learning Approach"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0026","question":"Which is/are the most cited paper(s) written by Alan Mantooth in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same. If there are multiple papers with the same citations, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Transformer Secondary Voltage Based Resonant Frequency Tracking for LLC Converter"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0027","question":"Which is/are the most cited paper(s) written by Kevin Lano in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same. If there are multiple papers with the same citations, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Introduction to the theme section on Agile model-driven engineering"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0028","question":"Which co-author of Weike Jin has the highest total citations for all their co-authored papers in the DBLP citation network?  Papers with the same title are considered the same. If there are multiple collaborators with the same citations, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Aoxiong Yin; Jinglin Liu"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0029","question":"Which co-author of Christine Gommenginger has the highest total citations for all their co-authored papers in the DBLP citation network?  Papers with the same title are considered the same. If there are multiple collaborators with the same citations, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Giuseppe Foti; Meric Srokosz"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0030","question":"Which co-author of Rolf Bagge has the highest total citations for all their co-authored papers in the DBLP citation network?  Papers with the same title are considered the same. If there are multiple collaborators with the same citations, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Janus Bager Kristensen; Luke Murray; Marcel Borowski"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0031","question":"Which co-author of Daniel Kaufer has the highest total citations for all their co-authored papers in the DBLP citation network?  Papers with the same title are considered the same. If there are multiple collaborators with the same citations, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Yingying Zhu"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0032","question":"Which co-author of Meijie Zhang has the highest total citations for all their co-authored papers in the DBLP citation network?  Papers with the same title are considered the same. If there are multiple collaborators with the same citations, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Fang Zhao"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0033","question":"Which co-author of Richard Howard has the highest total citations for all their co-authored papers in the DBLP citation network?  Papers with the same title are considered the same. If there are multiple collaborators with the same citations, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Larry Jackel; Riley Simmons-Edler; Daewon Lee"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0034","question":"Which co-author of Robyn Ritchie has the highest total citations for all their co-authored papers in the DBLP citation network?  Papers with the same title are considered the same. If there are multiple collaborators with the same citations, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Phillip Shreeves"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0035","question":"Which co-author of Moustafa H. Aly has the highest total citations for all their co-authored papers in the DBLP citation network?  Papers with the same title are considered the same. If there are multiple collaborators with the same citations, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Amit Grover"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0036","question":"Which co-author of Kaidi Cao has the highest total citations for all their co-authored papers in the DBLP citation network?  Papers with the same title are considered the same. If there are multiple collaborators with the same citations, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Maria Brbic"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0037","question":"Which co-author of Lulu Zhang has the highest total citations for all their co-authored papers in the DBLP citation network?  Papers with the same title are considered the same. If there are multiple collaborators with the same citations, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Xianbo Qiu; Yiqiang Fan"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0038","question":"Which co-author of Basile L. Agba has the highest total citations for all their co-authored papers in the DBLP citation network?  Papers with the same title are considered the same. If there are multiple collaborators with the same citations, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Mourad Debbabi; LebelBernard; Ribal Atallah"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0039","question":"Which co-author of Yakun Xie has the highest total citations for all their co-authored papers in the DBLP citation network?  Papers with the same title are considered the same. If there are multiple collaborators with the same citations, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Weilian Li; Ya Hu"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0040","question":"Which co-author of Daniel O’Keeffe has the highest total citations for all their co-authored papers in the DBLP citation network?  Papers with the same title are considered the same. If there are multiple collaborators with the same citations, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Jordy Gennissen"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0041","question":"Which co-author of Pingchuan Ke has the highest total citations for all their co-authored papers in the DBLP citation network?  Papers with the same title are considered the same. If there are multiple collaborators with the same citations, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Kening Zhu"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0042","question":"How many accumulated citations do papers collaborated by Alejandro Beacco and Mel Slater have in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":"11"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0043","question":"How many accumulated citations do papers collaborated by Ehrenmüller Julia and Allen Peter have in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":"0"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0044","question":"How many accumulated citations do papers collaborated by Yaqian Dun and Kefei Tu have in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":"24"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0045","question":"How many accumulated citations do papers collaborated by Tomi Kinnunen and Andreas Nautsch have in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":"25"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0046","question":"How many accumulated citations do papers collaborated by Ernesto Tarantino and Ivanoe De Falco have in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":"3"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0047","question":"How many accumulated citations do papers collaborated by Yunqiu Wu and Yiming Yu have in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":"6"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0048","question":"How many accumulated citations do papers collaborated by X Chen and Chengwen Xing have in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":"14"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0049","question":"How many accumulated citations do papers collaborated by Arren Glover and Marco Monforte have in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":"0"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0050","question":"How many accumulated citations do papers collaborated by Matthias Wright and Arthur Heimbrecht have in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":"27"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0051","question":"How many accumulated citations do papers collaborated by Avijeet Ghosh and Sujata Ghosh have in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":"0"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0052","question":"How many accumulated citations do papers collaborated by Ethan A. Chi and Julian Salazar have in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":"32"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0053","question":"How many accumulated citations do papers collaborated by Idaku Ishii and Kohei Shimasaki have in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":"0"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0054","question":"How many accumulated citations do papers collaborated by P. Agathoklis and Chamith Wijenayake have in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":"4"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0055","question":"How many accumulated citations do papers collaborated by Geerten van de Kaa and George Papachristos have in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":"0"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0056","question":"What is the total number of papers authored by Alessandro Margara and collaborators plus those written by collaborators and other people? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":2}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0057","question":"What is the total number of papers authored by Yuh-Show Tsai and collaborators plus those written by collaborators and other people? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":2}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0058","question":"What is the total number of papers authored by Franco Milicchio and collaborators plus those written by collaborators and other people? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":1}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0059","question":"What is the total number of papers authored by Zhilin Huang and collaborators plus those written by collaborators and other people? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":2}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0060","question":"What is the total number of papers authored by Iris Dominguez-Catena and collaborators plus those written by collaborators and other people? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":1}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0061","question":"What is the total number of papers authored by Alemitu Mequanint Bezabih and collaborators plus those written by collaborators and other people? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":1}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0062","question":"What is the total number of papers authored by Tabib Wennie and collaborators plus those written by collaborators and other people? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":4}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0063","question":"What is the total number of papers authored by Evangelos Kanoulas and collaborators plus those written by collaborators and other people? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":2}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0064","question":"What is the total number of papers authored by Zijie Yang and collaborators plus those written by collaborators and other people? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":2}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0065","question":"What is the total number of papers authored by Chunlei Sun and collaborators plus those written by collaborators and other people? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":18}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0066","question":"What is the total number of papers authored by Camille Gobert and collaborators plus those written by collaborators and other people? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":6}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0067","question":"What is the total number of papers authored by Xiaoqin Zang and collaborators plus those written by collaborators and other people? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":1}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0068","question":"What is the total number of papers authored by Marco Robol and collaborators plus those written by collaborators and other people? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":3}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0069","question":"What is the total number of papers authored by Jhon Bueno Vesga and collaborators plus those written by collaborators and other people? Papers with the same title are considered the same.","answer":1}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0070","question":"Who collaborated with Christopher Liaw most in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same. If there are multiple authors with the same number of collaborations, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Hassan Ashtiani"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0071","question":"Who collaborated with Cosmin Iulian Gosoiu most in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same. If there are multiple authors with the same number of collaborations, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Doru Anastasiu Popescu; Daniel Nijloveanu"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0072","question":"Who collaborated with Riccardo M. G. Ferrari most in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same. If there are multiple authors with the same number of collaborations, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Andre M. H. Teixeira"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0073","question":"Who collaborated with Aswathnarayan Radhakrishnan most in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same. If there are multiple authors with the same number of collaborations, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Roman Ilin; Nicholas Kashani Motlagh"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0074","question":"Who collaborated with Kaiqi Xiong most in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same. If there are multiple authors with the same number of collaborations, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Yufeng Xin; Ryan Luley"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0075","question":"Who collaborated with Eli Bronstein most in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same. If there are multiple authors with the same number of collaborations, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"SF Smith; Isaac K. Isukapati"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0076","question":"Who collaborated with Mong Li Lee most in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same. If there are multiple authors with the same number of collaborations, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Wynne Hsu; Sandareka Wickramanayake"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0077","question":"Who collaborated with Jiaguo Liu most in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same. If there are multiple authors with the same number of collaborations, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Yang De Marinis; Rui Gao"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0078","question":"Who collaborated with Emma Lejeune most in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same. If there are multiple authors with the same number of collaborations, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Christopher S. Chen; Kehan Zhang"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0079","question":"Who collaborated with Jianghua Duan most in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same. If there are multiple authors with the same number of collaborations, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Yongsheng Ou; Sheng Xu"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0080","question":"Who collaborated with Bibhudatta Sahoo most in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same. If there are multiple authors with the same number of collaborations, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Ashok Kumar Turuk"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0081","question":"Who collaborated with Van Anh Huynh-Thu most in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same. If there are multiple authors with the same number of collaborations, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Antonio Sutera; Louis Wehenkel; Pierre Geurts"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0082","question":"Who collaborated with Georgios Portokalidis most in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same. If there are multiple authors with the same number of collaborations, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Nikos Triandopoulos; Chengbin Pang"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0083","question":"Who collaborated with Yubo Xie most in the DBLP citation network? Papers with the same title are considered the same. If there are multiple authors with the same number of collaborations, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Anuradha Welivita; Pearl Pu"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0084","question":"What institutions participated in the study of 'A Study of the Application of Weight Distributing Method Combining Sentiment Dictionary and TF-IDF for Text Sentiment Analysis' in the DBLP citation network? Same institutions are considered the same. If there are multiple institutions, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"BNU, Collaborat Innovat Ctr Assessment Basic Educ Qual, Beijing 100875, Peoples R China"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0085","question":"What institutions participated in the study of 'Provably Secure Authentication Approach for Data Security in Cloud Using Hashing, Encryption, and Chebyshev-Based Authentication' in the DBLP citation network? Same institutions are considered the same. If there are multiple institutions, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Shaqra Univ, Shaqraa, Saudi Arabia; Univ Salford, Coll Comp Sci & Engn, Salford, Lancs, England; Riyadh Elm Univ, Riyadh, Saudi Arabia"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0086","question":"What institutions participated in the study of 'Finite-Time Output Synchronization and H ∞ Output Synchronization of Coupled Neural Networks With Multiple Output Couplings' in the DBLP citation network? Same institutions are considered the same. If there are multiple institutions, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Science Program, Texas A&M University at Qatar, Doha, Qatar; School of Computer Science and Technology, Tiangong University, Tianjin, China; Science and Technology on Aircraft Control Laboratory, School of Automation Science and Electrical Engineering, Beihang University, Beijing, China; Tianjin Key Laboratory of Autonomous Intelligence Technology and Systems, School of Computer Science and Technology, Tiangong University, Tianjin, China"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0087","question":"What institutions participated in the study of '2D-FRFT BASED FREQUENCY SHIFT-INVARIANT DIGITAL IMAGE ENCRYPTION' in the DBLP citation network? Same institutions are considered the same. If there are multiple institutions, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Ryerson Univ, Dept Elect Comp & Biomed Engn, Toronto, ON, Canada; Zhengzhou Univ, Sch Informat Engn, Zhengzhou, Peoples R China"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0088","question":"What institutions participated in the study of 'Digital Transformation Capability Maturity Model Enabling The Assessment Of Industrial Manufacturers' in the DBLP citation network? Same institutions are considered the same. If there are multiple institutions, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Univ Cambridge, Inst Mfg, Dept Engn, 17 Charles Babbage Rd, Cambridge CB3 0FS, England"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0089","question":"What institutions participated in the study of 'Large-Scale English-Japanese Simultaneous Interpretation Corpus: Construction And Analyses With Sentence-Aligned Data' in the DBLP citation network? Same institutions are considered the same. If there are multiple institutions, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Nara Inst Sci & Technol, Nara, Japan"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0090","question":"What institutions participated in the study of 'Autonomous Repeat Image Feature Tracking (Autorift) And Its Application For Tracking Ice Displacement' in the DBLP citation network? Same institutions are considered the same. If there are multiple institutions, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"CALTECH, Div Geol & Planetary Sci, Pasadena, CA 91125 USA; CALTECH, Jet Prop Lab, 4800 Oak Grove Dr, Pasadena, CA 91109 USA"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0091","question":"What institutions participated in the study of 'Hardware Limitations to Secure C-ITS: Experimental Evaluation and Solutions' in the DBLP citation network? Same institutions are considered the same. If there are multiple institutions, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"University of Modena, Modena MO, Italy"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0092","question":"What institutions participated in the study of 'PupilMeter: Modeling User Preference with Time-Series Features of Pupillary Response' in the DBLP citation network? Same institutions are considered the same. If there are multiple institutions, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Hunan Univ, Coll Comp Sci & Elect Engn, Changsha, Peoples R China"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0093","question":"What institutions participated in the study of 'High-Bandwidth Suspension Resonance Analysis of In-Wheel Motor Vehicle Using Multibody Dynamics' in the DBLP citation network? Same institutions are considered the same. If there are multiple institutions, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Engineering Consulting Services, Siemens Industry Software NV, Leuven, Belgium; Graduate School of Frontier Science, The University of Tokyo, Chiba, Japan"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0094","question":"What institutions participated in the study of 'Capacity Planning for an Electric Vehicle Charging Station Considering Fuzzy Quality of Service and Multiple Charging Options' in the DBLP citation network? Same institutions are considered the same. If there are multiple institutions, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Department of Industrial and Systems Engineering, The Hong Kong Polytechnic University, Hong Kong, SAR, China"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0095","question":"What institutions participated in the study of 'Monotone Fuzzy Rule Interpolation for Practical Modeling of the Zero-Order TSK Fuzzy Inference System' in the DBLP citation network? Same institutions are considered the same. If there are multiple institutions, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Universiti Malaysia Sarawak, Kota Samarahan, Malaysia; Institute for Intelligent Systems Research and Innovation, Deakin University, Geelong, VIC, Australia; Universiti Kebangsaan Malaysia, Bangi, Malaysia"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0096","question":"What institutions participated in the study of 'New Constructions of Group-Invariant Butson Hadamard Matrices' in the DBLP citation network? Same institutions are considered the same. If there are multiple institutions, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"DigiPen Inst Technol Singapore, Dept Math & Phys, Singapore 139660, Singapore"}
{"qid":"hard-dblp-0097","question":"What institutions participated in the study of 'Zero-Aware Low-Precision RNS Scaling Scheme' in the DBLP citation network? Same institutions are considered the same. If there are multiple institutions, separate them with semicolon and space '; '.","answer":"Queens Univ Belfast, Sch Elect Elect Engn & Comp Sci, Belfast BT7 1NN, Antrim, North Ireland"}
